<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' ?>
<editorial>
	<header>
	</header>
	<body>
		<title_1>The iPod range: a concentrate of high technology and design</title_1>
		<title_2>La gamme iPod : un concentré de technologie et de design</title_2>
		<title_3>La Línea iPod: un concentrado de tecnoloía y diseno</title_3>
		<subheading_1>NEW: Discover the new iPod Touch!</subheading_1>
		<subheading_2>NOUVEAU : Découvrez le nouvel iPod Touch !</subheading_2>
		<subheading_3>NUEVO: Descubre el nuevo iPod Touch!</subheading_3>
		<paragraph_1>&lt;p&gt;Our iPod range has been designed to allow you to rediscover your music thanks to a ludic, animated, dynamic interface with an incredible quality sound and a unique design. 	                From the iPod Shuffle, the tiniest music player in the world, to the iPod Nano through the iPod Touch, find the iPod that looks like you and carry your universe (music, pictures, videos and games) everywhere with you. 	                Enter now in the Apple community by ordering your iPod online.&lt;/p&gt;</paragraph_1>
		<paragraph_2>&lt;p&gt;Notre gamme iPod a été conçue pour vous permettre de redécouvrir votre musique grâce à une interface ludique, animée, dynamique, un son d’une qualité exceptionnelle et un design unique. 	                De l’iPod Shuffle, baladeur le plus portable du monde, à l’iPod Nano en passant par l’iPod Touch, trouvez l’iPod qui vous ressemble et emportez votre univers (musique, photos, vidéos, jeux) partout avec vous. 	                Entrez dès maintenant dans la communauté Apple en commandant votre iPod directement en ligne.&lt;/p&gt;</paragraph_2>
		<paragraph_3>&lt;p&gt;Nuestra línea iPod ha sido diseñado para permitirle de redescubrir su música a través de una interfaz  divertida, animada, dinámica, un sonido de una calidad excepcional y un diseño único. 	                Del iPod Shuffle, walkman más portátil del mundo, hasta el Nano iPod, pasando por el iPod Touch, encontran el iPod que más le convenga y lleva su mundo (música, fotos, vídeos, juegos) a todas partes. Entra ahora en la comunidad de Apple comprando su IPod directamente en línea.&lt;/p&gt;</paragraph_3>
		<home_logo_link>http://www.prestashop.com</home_logo_link>
		<logo_subheading_1> The iPod range</logo_subheading_1>
		<logo_subheading_2> La gamme iPod</logo_subheading_2>
		<logo_subheading_3> La Línea iPod</logo_subheading_3>
	</body>
</editorial>
